# MARSHALL BRUNER

Denver, CO

**८** +1 970-568-6162 **☑** brunerm99@gmail.com **iii** <u>marshall-bruner</u> **?** <u>brunerm99</u> **❖** <u>brunerm99</u>

## **OBJECTIVE**

I am pursuing a transition into the Data Science industry. My motivation has pushed me to learn the necessary tools and apply them to personal projects alongside my demanding job in the aerospace industry. I believe my expertise as an RF engineer, specifically in the signal processing field, gives me an interesting perspective to contribute to a team.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Ball Aerospace Jun. 2021 — Present

RF Engineer

• Used Python knowledge to create useful plotting and RF analysis tools

- Simulated, designed, and tested an RF Front-End PWB at extreme temperatures
- Debugged complex, mission-critical RF boards under strict time constraints
- Built an embedded webpage used to interact with a phased array antenna
- High-power testing of real antenna loads

# Colorado State University

Graduate Research Assistant — Thesis

Jan. 2021 — May 2022

Fort Collins, CO

Broomfield, CO

- $\bullet\,$  Design, schematic, and layout of a modular, X-band, FMCW drone radar
- Signal processing / data visualization for Analog Device's FMCW Phaser Board
- Work for the Phaser Board was presented at IMS 2022 and IEEE-APS 2022
- Will personally be presenting work at the International Phased Array Symposium
- Built a server to host and display real-time and historical radar data using Post-GreSQL, Flask, Python

CHILL Radar Lab

May 2020 — May 2021

Greeley, CO

- <u>Lab Assistant</u>
  Built a real-time radar display to easily display and animate radar data
  - Performed characterizations and measurements of radar equipment

## **EDUCATION**

# Colorado State University

M.S. Electrical Engineering — GPA: 3.9

Jan. 2021 — May 2022

Fort Collins, CO

Fort Collins, CO

Thesis - Design, Deployment, and Cost Considerations for DARMA; A Low-Cost and Lightweight FMCW Radar

#### Colorado State University

B.S. Electrical Engineering — GPA: 3.47

Aug. 2017 — May 2021

#### **PROJECTS**

### 5G Electronics Senior Design Project

Jun. 2020 — May 2021

- Simulated, assembled, and measured a full 5G receiver system
- Created teaching documentation for a 5G transmitter and receiver for FR1 and FR2 frequency bands
- Experience using FieldFox, EMPro, ADS, SystemVue

## Fuzzy Logic Clutter Filter

Nov. 2020 — Dec. 2020

• Applied the Fuzzy Logic machine learning technique to radar data as a clutter filter

## **Environment-Mapping Car**

Nov. 2020 — Dec. 2020

• Built and programmed battery-powered car with attached ultrasonic sensor for mobile mapping of the surrounding environment

#### SKILLS & ABILITIES

Languages: Python, SQL, C, Bash, Matlab, JavaScript, HTML, CSS

Technologies / Tools: Git, LATEX, Linux, Docker, PostGreSQL/TimescaleDB, Flask, Celery (Distributed Tasks)

Communication: Excellent Technical Communication and Presentation Skills, Experience Presenting PDR/CDRs,

Technical Paper/Presentation Formatting, Concise Code Documentation